Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Providers - Projection Materials. 1998 (Box 99)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Providers - Film, TV, Editing Media. 1998 (Box 99)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Providers - Lights. 1998 (Box 99)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Providers - Sound Recordings. 1998 (Box 99)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Providers - Music 1998 (Box 99)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Providers - Sound. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Design - Photos. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Design 2 of 2. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Design 1 of 2. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Scripts 3 of 3. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Scripts 2 of 3. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Scripts 1 of 3. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Prototype Document Draft 2 of 2. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Prototype Document Draft 1 of 2. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Budgets 3 of 3. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Budgets 2 of 3. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Budgets 1 of 3. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Personal. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Email. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Memos/Tranmittals. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Current. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Business. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Contracts. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Permissions. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Feasibility Study. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Architecture. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. RFP Forms. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Contact Sheets. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Schedules. 1998 (Box 100)
  - American History Workshop - N.U.R.F.C. Jewish Museum. 1998 (Box 100)
  - Smithsonian Flag Hall. 1983 (Box 101)
  - Smithsonian Flag Hall. P.R./Press 1983 (Box 101)
  - Smithsonian Flag Hall. Flag Painting 3 of 3. 1983 (Box 101)
  - Smithsonian Flag Hall. Flag Painting 2 of 3. 1983 (Box 101)
  - Smithsonian Flag Hall. Flag Painting 1 of 3. 1983 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits: Star Spangled Banner - Flag Hall. 1983 (Box 101)
  - NSO - SLAVA. Gala. Background. 1986 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. 1987 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Background. 1987 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Other Festivals. 1987 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Budget. 1987 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Transmittals. 1987 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Memoranda. 1987 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. 1989 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Research 3 of 3. 1989 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Research 2 of 3. 1989 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Research 1 of 3. 1989 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Contact Lists. 1989 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. 1990 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Music - TV Series - Early Proposals. 1990 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Music - TV Series - Early Memos 1990 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Music - TV Series - Current Proposals. 1990 (Box 101)
  - NSO - Kennedy Center Summer Festival. Music - TV Series - Proposal. 1990 (Box 101)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. 1983 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Vendors - Tents and Fabrics. 1983 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Portable Performance Facility 1986 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Portable Performance Facility Vendors - Tent Structures. 1986 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Portable Performance Facility Fabric. 1986 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Portable Performance Facility 1998 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Portable Performance Facility Truck, tractor, cabs. 1998 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Portable Performance Facility Preliminary Design (Binder). 1998 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. MET/PHIL PKS IV. TV Projections. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion Parks IV. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion Parks IV. Projection Ring. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opening Concert for C. Hall. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opening Concert for C. Hall. Projections Cut Slides. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opening Concert for C. Hall. Projections Final Slides. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opening Concert for C. Hall. Projections PPWK, Disks 8/20/90. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opening Concert for C. Hall. Correspondence. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL IV. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL IV. Business. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL IV Opening Concert for C. Hall. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL IV Opening Concert for C. Hall. Lighting - Projections and Light Q's Plot. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL IV Opening Concert for C. Hall. Lighting - Instrument Schedule and Channel Hook-Up. 1990 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting- Philharmonic Only- Channel Groupings Final. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting- Philharmonic Only- Instrument Schedule Final. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting- Philharmonic Only- Individual Con. Running Sheets Final. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting-Philharmonic Only- Cue Sheets- Final. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting- Stage Lighting Manual Book 1, 3 of 3. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting-Stage Lighting Manual Book 1, 2 of 3. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL Opera. Cons 2nd Half Season. Lighting- Stage Lighting Manual Book 1, 1 of 3. 1991 (Box 102)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Lighting-Stage Lighting Manual Book 2, 2 of 2. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Lighting- Stage Lighting Manual Book 2, 1 of 2. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Sound- Site Plans and Speaker Deployment. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Sound- MSI Manual 4 of 4. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Sound- MSI Manual 3 of 4. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Sound- MSI Manual 2 of 4. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Sound- MSI Manual 1 of 4. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Operations Manual 3 of 3. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Operations Manual 2 of 3. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Operations Manual 1 of 3. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Press/ Publicity. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Research. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Instrument Schedule Final. 1991 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. 1994 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Programs and Schedules, etc. 1994 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. 1996 (Box 103)
  - Carlos Moseley Pavilion. Bard Award. 1996 (Box 103)
  - Potential Projects. Grand Central Station. 1988 (Box 104)
  - Radio City Music Hall/Pier 84. 1990-1991 (Box 104)
  - Radio City Music Hall/Pier 84. Legal. 1990-1991 (Box 104)
  - Radio City Music Hall/Pier 84. General Release - Signed. 1990-1991 (Box 104)
  - Performing Arts - Fort Worth. Newspaper Articles. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Bugatti Exhibition. Vieri Salvadori. Correspondence. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Arlington Stadium. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Les Troyen - Metropolitan Opera House. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Les Troyen - Metropolitan Opera House. Press and Publicity - Reviews. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Les Troyen - Metropolitan Opera House. Press and Publicity - Programs. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Les Troyen - Metropolitan Opera House. Press and Publicity. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Les Troyen - Metropolitan Opera House. Correspondence. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Les Troyen - Metropolitan Opera House. Computer Disks. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Who's Who in America. 1993 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Program - Rostropovich Pravda Letter. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Program- Van Cliburn VTR Script. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Program- Solzhenitsyn Letter to Rostropovich. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Program- WETA’s Rundowns. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Program- PW Inc’s Rundowns and Scripts. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Program- Script. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Press from Concert. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Brochures and Programs. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Foliage Patterns. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Checklist for Stephen Aberg. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Salute to Slava Movement. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Schedule for Week of June 13-17. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Video Footage and Photograph Info. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Background Info and Press on Slava. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Photos of Slava. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Distribution of Materials- May 11. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Distribution of Materials- May 25. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Distribution of Materials-June 1. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Post Production Info and Correspondence. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Celebrity Host Contracts or Agents. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Paula Zahn’s Bio and Headshot. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Possibilities for Reference. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Artists. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Artists’ Tickets. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Artists to Date. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. PW’s Notes. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Correspondence. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Transmittals. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Contracts. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Contact Sheets. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Computer Disks. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Salute to Salva. NSO. Mstislav Rostropovich and Galina Vishnevskaya Cons. Claude Samuel- Book. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Video and Photo Research. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Artistic- Still Photos. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. List of Credits PW Inc and Photo. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Artistic Light cues. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Artistic Info on Space at Carver Cultural Center. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Artistic Script Materials from Carnegie Hall, 1988. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Artistic Script Materials from Proms in London. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Press and Publicity. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Program. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Maps of San Antonio. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Master Checklist. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Schedules/Itineraries. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Business-Budget. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Correspondence. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Transmittals. 1994 (Box 104)
  - Cry the Beloved Country, San Antonio Symph. Contact Sheet. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Truck and Scissors Lift Research. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Background. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Unit Set Proposal June 3 Final Proposal. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Design. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Budget. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Item List. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Correspondence. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Memorandum. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Transmittals. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Verdi Proposal. Contract. 1994 (Box 104)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Unit Set Design. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Unit Set Bids Received. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Unit Set Budget. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Unit Set Memorandum. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Unit Set Transmittals. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Unit Set Contracts. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Nabucco. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Un Giorno Di Regno. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Oberto. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Photos. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Background. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Research. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Schedules. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Press and Public Relations. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Bids Received. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Correspondence. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Memoranda. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Transmittals. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Contracts. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 Season Contact Sheet. 1994 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Giovanni D’Arco. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. I Due Foscari. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Ernani. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. I Lombardi. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Design. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Press and Public Relations. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Bids Received. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Budget. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Correspondence. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Memoranda. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Transmittals. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 Season Contact Sheet. 1995 (Box 105)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. Computer Disks. 1995 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Architecture Computer Renderings. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Architecture Addenda to Drawings 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Architecture Additional Drawings. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Architecture Plans as of 3-15-99. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Archive General Info. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Fire Escape. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Program/ Posters. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Photos/Scenic Renderings. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Photos/Call Center. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research The Shubert Organization. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research The Shubert Brothers. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Additional Theatres. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Winter Garden. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Shubert. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Royale. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Plymouth. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Music Box. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Majestic. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Lyceum. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Golden. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Broadhurst. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Theatres Booth. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Design Duplicate Photographs. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Design Photos: Broadway and Times Square. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Shubert History 6 of 6, Current. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Shubert History 5 of 6, 1940’s. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Shubert History 4 of 6, 1920’s. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Shubert History 3 of 6, Sam’s Death. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Shubert History 2 of 6, Arrival in NY. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Shubert History 1 of 6, Syracuse. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Research Photos: Costume Renderings. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Artwork for Marquee/ Light Box Murals. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Design- Photoshop Renderings. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Vendors- LED/LCD. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Item Chart. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Contract. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Business. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Budget. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Meeting Notes. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Schedules. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. Contact Sheet. 1999 (Box 105)
  - Boston Pops. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Xmas Pops- Press and Publicity 2 of 2. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Xmas Pops- Press and Publicity 1 of 2. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Xmas Pops Photos 2 of 2. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Xmas Pops Photos 1 of 2. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Xmas Pops Budget. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Xmas Pops Memoranda. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Program Book. 1994 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Press and Public Relations. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Photo Research. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Photos. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Lighting. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Scenery. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Item List. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Budget. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Schedules. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Meeting Notes. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Memoranda. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Correspondence. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Transmittals. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Contracts. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Contact Sheet. 1995 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Photos. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Scenery. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Press. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Lighting. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Budget. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Memoranda. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Transmittals. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Contact Sheet. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Carnegie Hall Press and Publicity. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Carnegie Hall. 1996 (Box 106)
  - Boston Pops. Youth Concert. 1996 (Box 106)
  - BSO Spring Pops. Press and PR. 1997 (Box 107)
  - BSO Xmas Pops. Programs. 1997 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. Lighting. 1997 (Box 107)
  - BSO Xmas Pops. Press and PR. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Spring Pops. Memoranda. Production. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. Budget. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. Schedules. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. Memoranda. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. Transmittals. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Pops. General. 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Model. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. CAD Drawings Printout. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Disks and Drawings. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Disks Only. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Painting. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Risers. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Storage. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Sound Absorbing Panels. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research TV Production. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Projection. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Lighting. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Wiring. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Research Rigging. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Report 11-21-95. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Report Notes. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Memoranda. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Meeting Notes. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Transmittals. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Calendar. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Contracts. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Historical Research. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Polsheck Report. 1995 (Box 107)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Reduced Version Without the Financials 3-25-96. (2 Books) 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Reduced Version With Financials 3-25-96. (1Book) 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Rough Changes for 12-10-95 Edition. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Early Drafts. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Outline. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Original Bible Updated Through 12-10-95. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Work Copy. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Bible of Report- 3-25-96. (3 parts) 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Photo Research Sight Survey 2 of 2. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Photo Research Sight Survey 1 of 2. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Photo Research. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Engineering. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Business. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Correspondence. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan. Transmittals. 1995-1996 (Box 108)
  - BSO Lighting. 1996 (Box 109)